Tyler Shively

www.linkedin.com/in/tylershively ~ tyshively50@gmail.com ~ Las Vegas, NV ~ 702.376.6244

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

Training: Trained new employees on work protocols; conducted new-hire programming

Customer Service: Experience assisting diverse customers, problem-solving, and resolving escalated issues

Communication: Interpersonal, collaboration, and presentation skills with people of diverse backgrounds and importance

Leadership: Managed a team of people with a diverse set of skills and backgrounds for a common goal, Manage 25+

children in camp activities, understand when problems need solving.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, College of Aviation, Science, and Tech

Unmanned Aircraft Systems

Lewis University, Romeoville, IL

Advanced Honors Diploma

Construction Technology

Northwest Career and Technical Academy, Las Vegas, NV

Expected: December 2023

GPA: 3.0/4.0

Graduated: May 2019

WORK EXPERIENCE

Delivery Amazon Associate

Amazon Delivery

- Handle thousands of packages daily with various sizes and weights
- Solved diverse problems within the center
- Solved diverse problems with the drivers
- Train new employees as to each role's job in the warehouse
- Collaborate with managers and leaders to update the flow and concerns with sortation
- Help other associates meet quotas and timed tasks

The UPS Store Associate

May 2020 – August 2020

May 2021 – August 2021

Las Vegas, NV

- Train 1-2 new employees each month on store policies, upselling, and customer service
- Assist diverse array of customers with their selections of boxes and purchases
- Process 50+ cash and credit transactions daily; balance cash drawer
- Resolve customer complaints to ensure satisfaction and promote repeat business
- Resolve customer problems allowing

Southern Nevada Lacrosse Association Referee

May 2018- August 2018

Las Vegas, NV

- Referee for U8-U10
- Resolving escalated and critical times during the games

HONORS AND AWARDS

- Dean's List, Lewis University, two semesters
- Recipient, NV Energy Endowment Scholarship, 2019
- OSHA Certified, 2018
- Recipient, Athletic Scholarship Men's Lacrosse, 2019-Present

LEADERSHIP, ACTIVITIES, AND VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

- Member, Lewis University Men's Lacrosse Team, 2019 Present
- Member, Palo Verde Men's Lacrosse Team, Captain, 2016 2019
- Volunteer Mentor, Camp Invention, June 2017 and June 2018

LANGUAGES AND COMPUTER SKILLS

- Proficient in MS Word, MS Excel, MS PowerPoint, Google Docs/Forms/Slides/Sheets
- Familiar with Python
- Proficient in major social media outlets including Instagram, YouTube, Pinterest, LinkedIn, Instagram, and Twitter; able to promote community outreach activities and events via social media posts